

Sofia Carvalho

I'm a software developer with technical skills and a practical approach. In addition to programming, I stand out for being an effective communicator and enjoy helping the team overcome challenges.

Approaching new challenges with enthusiasm, I am ever-ready to learn and evolve. I made a deliberate shift in my career because of my enduring interest in technology. Even during my time in accounting, I relished exploring software to optimize processes. The transition into programming has been a fulfilling journey, where I thrive in finding solutions to various challenges.

I love helping my colleagues. I believe that the success of a project is intrinsically linked to collaboration and mutual support.

I maintain good interpersonal relationships, which are a reflection of the importance I attach to teamwork.

I am ready to bring my experience and attitude to contribute to the team's success.

Contacts



+351 919665979



□ ascarvalho77@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/sofia-carvalho-28a4765b/



Porto, Portugal

Skills

Java

Kotlin

Swift

PHP

Javascript

HTML5

CSS3

Laravel

Angular

SQL

UML

Bootstrap

С

C++

Microsoft Office

Languages

Portuguese

English



Education and Training

Software Developer

2023-current

CESAE - Centro para Desenvolvimento de Competências Digitais

Degree in computer engineering

2021-current

UAB - Universidades Aberta

ISTQB Foundation Level Certification

2023

PSTOB

Postgraduate in Taxation

IPCA - Instituto Politécnico do Cávado e do Ave

Specialization in audit

2010-2012

ISCAP - Instotuto Superior de Contabilidade e Administração

Degree in accounting and administration

2005-2010

ISCAP - Instotuto Superior de Contabilidade e Administração

Experience

Certified Accountant

2014-2019

MX Consulting, Lda

Accountant

2012-2014

Serious-Gabinete de Contabilidade.Lda

Accountant

2010-2012

Queirós & Batista, Lda